<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<modules><module><id><![CDATA[42]]></id><name><![CDATA[leguide]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[LeGuide.com]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[LeGuide.com allows you to make your site and your products known to millions of shoppers wanting to buy products and thus gaining the loyalty of new customers]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[LeGuide.com allows you to make your site and your products known to millions of shoppers wanting to buy products and thus gaining the loyalty of new customers. It is&nbsp;a fantastic window for e-merchants!      The LeGuide.com Group is the number 1 independent French publisher of shopping guides, shopping-based search engines and price comparison on the internet. It already exists in 14 countries and 9 different languages.  LeGuide.com has been a trusted partner of shoppers and merchants since 1998: the former, it helps to find the most interesting product offers online and the latter it helps in improving their visibility and developing their operations.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module gives you the opportunity to develop your business and highlight your site your best deals!    When you sell products online, it&rsquo;s essential that potential customers can find their way to your site. Whether they are trying to unearth a particular product or are simply trying to find the cheapest offer, buyers are using shopping guides more and more; having a listing on a price comparison website is therefore vital if you want to make yourself known to millions of buyers about to make a purchase and thus boost your sales.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[smart_shopping]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.8.14]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.6.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[87]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.3]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/42.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/comparison-shopping-prestashop/42-leguidecom.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[367]]></id><name><![CDATA[banipmod]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Ban IP addresses]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Are spammers and fraudulent transactions affecting your revenue?   Ban their IP address to restrict their access to your online store]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Are spammers and fraudulent transactions affecting your revenue?   Ban their IP address to restrict their access to your online store.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Choose between redirecting them to another website or allowing them to browse but denying them access to make purchases.  Stop wasting time and money by banning unreliable customers.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[17]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.4]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/367.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/367-ban-ip-addresses.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[1504]]></id><name><![CDATA[upstracking]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[UPS Delivery Status]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[UPS, the #1 package delivery service in the United States, is a key player in ecommerce]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[UPS, the #1 package delivery service in the United States, is a key player in ecommerce. Offering UPS as a form of delivery is crucial for customers looking for speedy, tracked and dependable delivery.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[18]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.8]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1504.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/shipping-logistics-delivery-prestashop-modules/1504-ups-delivery-status.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[1615]]></id><name><![CDATA[gshopping]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Google Shopping]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Easily export your entire product catalog to Google Shopping, the new Google developed price comparison service!    Note: A subscription to a third party service is required in order to use the module]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Easily export your entire product catalog to Google Shopping, the new Google developed price comparison service!    Note: A subscription to a third party service is required in order to use the module.  Please subscribe to the service before making this purchase.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Product Listing Ads drive traffic and sales to your website or local store by showing online shoppers rich images and details of items you sell.    Product Listing Ads appear when someone searches for your products on google.com and google.com/shopping. Customers who click on your ad will be directed to your website where they can buy your item.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[smart_shopping]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.12]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[108]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.9]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1615.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/comparison-shopping-prestashop/1615-google-shopping.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[2191]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestanotify]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Box Notification (Popup)]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Sale more with this module!  Merchants often need to put forward a possible warning, a call to action or just a greeting!  With this module, inform your customers of a flash sale, of sales, promotions]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Sale more with this module!  Merchants often need to put forward a possible warning, a call to action or just a greeting!  With this module, inform your customers of a flash sale, of sales, promotions, and guide them on their arrival in your online shop.  Very easy to use: you only have one image or text to add, create a link on the page a match, and you make additional sales in the category of your choice.  ﻿]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Box Notification helps you to increase your sales!]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.7.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[92]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2191.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/2191-box-notification-popup.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[2501]]></id><name><![CDATA[amazon]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Amazon Market Place]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Exclusive PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Exclusive PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[You can easily integrate your PrestaShop store to the world&rsquo;s top marketplace and significantly increase your sales. You import your orders into your PrestaShop store and centralize your stocks.    Managing your inventory efficiently and quickly honoring your Amazon orders allows you to increase the degree of customer satisfaction and thus automatically increase the rank of your seller performance.    The design of the module is based on the initial experience of online retailers. The module was developed by an online retailer for the service of his colleagues and it was developed by a team of professional developers, by making it easy to use and to have the maximum efficiency.    Your purchase is protected by free technical support that is provided unconditionally until the products are placed online and the first orders are imported.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.9.158]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.13]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[286]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.1]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2501.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[279.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[164.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/marketplace-prestashop-modules/2501-amazon-market-place.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[3162]]></id><name><![CDATA[webcallback]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Call Back]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Add the Call Back module to your online store to increase sales!   Nothing is more frustrating than getting through to a company, just to be put on hold]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Add the Call Back module to your online store to increase sales!   Nothing is more frustrating than getting through to a company, just to be put on hold. Stop wasting customers&rsquo; time with the Call Back Module. Let customers leave their contact information for you to contact them at a convenient time. Capture customers you would have otherwise lost.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[36]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.8]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3162.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/3162-web-call-back.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[3252]]></id><name><![CDATA[printlabels]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Print Labels Pro]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Save time during your shipping process by mass printing labels! The Print Shipping Labels Pro Module lets you add fields in bulk to shipping labels to optimize printing jobs]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Save time during your shipping process by mass printing labels! The Print Shipping Labels Pro Module lets you add fields in bulk to shipping labels to optimize printing jobs.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.2.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[124]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.1]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3252.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/3252-print-labels.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[3438]]></id><name><![CDATA[auctions]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Auctions]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Auctions module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Auctions module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way. With a number of great features and intuitive interface, this is the best auctions module available for Prestashop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way. Auctions are the great way to attract and keep customers in your shop. You will be sure that customer is paying right price for your products. You don&#39;t have to negotiate prices with customers anymore. Managing auctions is very intuitive, and fully integrated with your shop. You will feel like it&#39;s not a module but integral part of the PrestaShop.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.13]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[34]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.6]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3438.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/3438-auctions.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges/></module><module><id><![CDATA[3511]]></id><name><![CDATA[priceminister]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PriceMinister]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Take advantage of the PriceMinister audience with its 2 million visitors a year and its 20 million subscribed members and boost your sales with your super PriceMinister store]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Take advantage of the PriceMinister audience with its 2 million visitors a year and its 20 million subscribed members and boost your sales with your super PriceMinister store.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With the PriceMinister for Prestashop module, your processing is automated, the products are exported directly to the PriceMinister marketplace and your orders are automatically imported and integrated into your Prestashop store.      You also automate communication with your customers: your order confirmations are sent directly to the customer by email via the PriceMinister web service, customers are automatically notified and the status of your orders is automatically updated.    By using the PriceMinister module, you maintain control of your offer and product flows, you automatically import your orders without additional cost or subscription and your data exchanges are automated and free.    Integration is easy and convenient: you configure your module, your export becomes automatic and so you have no more data to manipulate    Implementing scheduled tasks is simple and automated thanks to compatibility with the Prestashop Cron task-scheduling editor module (free). Just click on a button to automatically integrate your scheduled tasks in the module. It is still possible to manually configure your tasks.    The module design is based on the online merchant experience. The module was conceived by an online merchant in the service of his colleagues and developed by professional developers, which gives it ease of use and maximum effectiveness.    Your purchase is protected by free technical support which is assured unconditionally up to the moment of making the products available online and the import of your first orders.    You must have a PriceMinister PRO account.    New version, PriceMinister v4: export XML, simplified configuration, native scheduled tasks, intelligent mapping, sleek design and improved ergonomics.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.13]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[63]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.2]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3511.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[179.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[244.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[144.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/marketplace-prestashop-modules/3511-priceminister.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[4932]]></id><name><![CDATA[mynewsletter]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Newsletter & Statistics]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[The best way to convert, build loyalty and keep in touch with customers is with our Newsletter with Statistics Module! This brilliant module helps you send gorgeous newsletters to customer groups -- a]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[The best way to convert, build loyalty and keep in touch with customers is with our Newsletter with Statistics Module! This brilliant module helps you send gorgeous newsletters to customer groups -- and help keep them coming back to shop!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Track the effectiveness of each newsletter. Every KPI you, as an online merchant, should monitor is available at your fingertips. These key statistics allow online merchants to monitor newsletters to see which work and which don&rsquo;t to improve newsletter mailings.    Additional benefits include:     Inform customers about sales, company or industry news, new products, etc.   Personalize newsletters (to echo your brand identity)   Build customer loyalty to your brand   Stay in touch with your customers    ]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.23]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.5.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[197]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4932.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.9]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/4932-newsletter-statistics.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[4982]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_seointernallinking]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Internal Linking]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Enhance your PrestaShop SEO    Internal linking&nbsp;is the creation of links between pages of your shop, using keywords you want to achieve a&nbsp;better place on Google.    To&nbsp;optimize the SEO of your website, it is essential to create an&nbsp;internal linking&nbsp;that will allow search engines to browse your shop in the most easy way as possible. The goal is to provide maximum informations with the least clicks deep.    SEO Internal Linking&nbsp;PrestaShop module optimizes the organization of navigation in your store, and plays an essential role in your&nbsp;SEO strategy.    Define the keywords on which you wish to be listed and their landing pages, and let the module create the links for you!    If you want to add automatic links in your categories descriptions, consider installing our PrestaShop module&nbsp;HTML On Descriptions.    Do we really need internal linking?    Internal linking strategy&nbsp;based on specific keywords is an optimization method that has proven its worth. Especially to enhance a content relevance.    Among the disadvantages, you should know that the installation of these links is long and tedious, and requires to&nbsp;follow SEO good practices, to not over-optimize (which would be detected by Google), and must be updated regularly to track changes in your catalog.    With this in mind, we have developed this module, allowing you to deploy thousands of cross links between your pages within minutes, while being sure to observe best practice guidelines of White Hat SEO.    It has been designed to support both SEO agencies and e-shop owners.  SEO Internal Linking&nbsp;is really simple to manage.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.10]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.1.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.13]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[19]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.5]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4982.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[204.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[124.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/seo-prestashop-modules/4982-seo-internal-linking.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[5132]]></id><name><![CDATA[shipwire]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Shipwire]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Enterprise logistics for everyone. Shipwire helps grow your sales while reducing time, cost and complexity]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Enterprise logistics for everyone. Shipwire helps grow your sales while reducing time, cost and complexity.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[3]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[5.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5132.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[149]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[204.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[124.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/shipping-logistics-delivery-prestashop-modules/5132-shipwire.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[5255]]></id><name><![CDATA[ordertaxprofitreport]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get perfect visibility on your shop&#39;s and products&#39; profitability !    The default PrestaShop installation does not provide a one-click tool that allows you to obtain important accounting and financial data: tax due, net sales volume after discounts and, most importantly,&nbsp;profit and profit margin.    Not only will this report provide you with all this data, but it will even allow you to answer questions like &quot;what percentage of total sales and / or profits does this specific brand, supplier or product category represent ?&quot;.    This stylish and pleasant AJAX based module allows you to generate different types of preformed reports with all this information. They can be viewed on screen in HTML format or exported as a CSV&nbsp;file to manipulate in Excel and / or import into any other information or accounting system.    This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011 PrestaShop Awards for Best module.      You are guaranteed to buy a quality module and to get fast and efficient tech support in case you need it.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.8.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.2.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.13]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[44]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.2]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5255.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[204.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[119.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/analytics-stats-prestashop-modules/5255-advanced-sales-tax-profit-and-profit-margin-reports.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[5275]]></id><name><![CDATA[productsbycategoryslider]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Slider - Products of same category]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Submit items of the same class on your product pages with this slider at the bottom of the page, and improve the navigation of your customers, along with your average basket!]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Submit items of the same class on your product pages with this slider at the bottom of the page, and improve the navigation of your customers, along with your average basket!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module allows you to make cross-selling of other products in each category, and increase your average shopping basket.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[slideshows]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[24]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.3]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5275.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/slideshows-prestashop-modules/5275-slider-products-of-same-category.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[5314]]></id><name><![CDATA[npaypalpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PayPal Payments Pro]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[PayPal is one of the world&#39;s most trusted online payment solutions. The PayPal Payments Pro Module allows you to start accepting credit card transactions immediately]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[PayPal is one of the world&#39;s most trusted online payment solutions. The PayPal Payments Pro Module allows you to start accepting credit card transactions immediately. With the PayPal Payments Pro module, create a streamlined checkout process that allows customers to pay for products online with a simple click of the mouse.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Paypal Pro is the solution tailored to your business:     Simply configure your Client ID and Secret key.   Accept payments in 21 currencies from 190 countries around the globe.   Industry-leading fraud and buyer protections keep you and your customers safe.   There are no setup fees or long-term contracts.   Supports One-page checkout.    &nbsp;  The combination of PrestaShop expertise and Paypal Payments Pro services is the perfect solution to sell online.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[51]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[5.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5314.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[179.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[204.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/payments-gateways-prestashop-modules/5314-paypal-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[5542]]></id><name><![CDATA[orderpreparation]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Easy order preparation]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Efficiently run your online store&rsquo;s operations with the Product Locator for warehouses module!   This module allows you export warehouse locations of each product by order number and product qua]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Efficiently run your online store&rsquo;s operations with the Product Locator for warehouses module!   This module allows you export warehouse locations of each product by order number and product quantity. After you&rsquo;ve exported the data, sort by it by quantity, supplier, warehouse location or product ID to expedite the picking process.    Save time precious processing time with this module!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[20]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.3]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5542.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/5542-easy-order-preparation.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[6059]]></id><name><![CDATA[cdiscount]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cdiscount Marketplace]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Sell your products on the Cdiscount marketplace: catalogue export, automatic updating of prices and stocks, retrieval and management of orders]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Sell your products on the Cdiscount marketplace: catalogue export, automatic updating of prices and stocks, retrieval and management of orders.  Beneficiate from 3-month subscription free when you register on Cdiscount !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[C Le March&eacute; is one of France&rsquo;s leading marketplaces.    Boost your sales! Make the most of the traffic generated by Cdiscount to sell your products and enjoy the numerous advantages which make Cdiscount such a success:  - payment in 4 instalments (fully supported by Cdiscount)  - multiple delivery methods, etc.    Cdiscount takes care of everything! Place your products for sale on the marketplace and manage your orders while Cdiscount takes care of the rest: traffic, easy and secure payment, marketing, etc.    1 single back office! Thanks to the Cdiscount for PrestaShop module, you no longer need to manage several different back offices.  In just a few clicks, connect your PrestaShop site to your Cdiscount store and post your products:  - Product descriptions are exported directly to the Cdiscount marketplace,  - Prices and inventories are automatically updated,  - Your orders will be directly imported and integrated into your PrestaShop store.    Practical and easy configuration! Once you have configured your module, exports are automatic meaning you no longer have any data to handle.    A module developed by an e-merchant for e-merchants! The module&rsquo;s design is based on the early experience of online retailers. It was created by an e-merchants&nbsp;for the benefit of fellow e-merchants&nbsp;and developed by a team of professional developers, resulting in maximum user friendliness and efficiency.    Free technical support! Your purchase is guaranteed by free technical support provided unconditionally until your products are placed online and your first orders are imported.      *This offer applies for merchants already registered on&nbsp;CleMarch&eacute;&nbsp;Marketplace and cannot be used in combination with&nbsp;any other ongoing&nbsp;Cdiscount.com&nbsp;offer.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.9.62]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.13]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[96]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.3]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6059.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[194.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[119.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/marketplace-prestashop-modules/6059-cdiscount-marketplace.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[6414]]></id><name><![CDATA[lgabonos]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Credit Notes / Memos - Cancellation of Invoices]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Create full credit notes / memos for any invoice you need to cancel. Issue the notes in PDF and send them to your clients]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Create full credit notes / memos for any invoice you need to cancel. Issue the notes in PDF and send them to your clients.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module allows you to create full credit notes for any invoices that have been issued and then cancelled.    With this module, you can issue credit notes by selecting the invoice you want to refund. It only works with issued invoices.    No more problems with invoices and journal entries. With this module, you avoid submitting invoices that have been cancelled.    You can also issue credit notes in PDF and send them to your clients.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Línea Gráfica]]></author><tab><![CDATA[billing_invoicing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.13]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[12]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.4]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6414.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[99.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[59.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/billing-invoicing-prestashop-modules/6414-credit-notes-memos-cancellation-of-invoices.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[7152]]></id><name><![CDATA[customfields]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Custom Fields]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Create unlimited number of custom fields for registration form. You can add all kinds of fields: text, text area, radio buttons, check boxes and select lists with unlimited number of options and more]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Create unlimited number of custom fields for registration form. You can add all kinds of fields: text, text area, radio buttons, check boxes and select lists with unlimited number of options and more.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[It's important to know about as much as possible about customers. It will help with better understanding of the clients habits and needs. That knowledge will allow e-merchant to improve it's services and finally make more profit of his business. Custom fields module in easy way allows you to create unlimited number of custom fields and get all required data about your customers that cannot be done with standard registration form. All fields can be validated with selected validation rule and can be viewed and editable in the backoffice.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><tab><![CDATA[content_management]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.13]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[30]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.6]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/7152.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/content-management/7152-custom-fields.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges/></module><module><id><![CDATA[7422]]></id><name><![CDATA[groupinc]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Price increment/discount by customer groups]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[This module lets you&nbsp;apply an increment or a discount to product price depending on the customer&#39;s group]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[This module lets you&nbsp;apply an increment or a discount to product price depending on the customer&#39;s group.  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[   Apply different price to&nbsp;the product&nbsp;depending on the group that customer belongs to   Apply a markup to your products    ]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.13]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[8]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/7422.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/7422-price-increment-discount-by-customer-groups.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges/></module><module><id><![CDATA[8244]]></id><name><![CDATA[ec_seo404]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO - disabled and deleted 301 redirect Products]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[End with 404 pages and referencing loss for disabled or deleted product]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[End with 404 pages and referencing loss for disabled or deleted product. You will be able to choose for each case a 301 (Ideal for SEO)]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Whenever a product is disabled or deleted, you will be able to assign a 301 redirect.  No need to turn your catalog to find out which product is not active or has been removed, you can see them with the module and react accordingly.  Not overload your HTACCESS file and therefore no notion necessary to make it work !  The SEO which existed to this product will be redirected in confidence to a similar product, category page, etc. ... And not lose all the SEO that page had.  With a color scheme, get in a glance the status of your references:  - Green =&gt; Redirection possible for disabled or deleted products, but the redirection is not active. - Orange =&gt; Redirection possible for disabled or deleted products, but the redirection is not active and no link is specified for the redirection. - Red =&gt; Redirection enabled, but no link! So page 404 as usual!]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Ether Création]]></author><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.13]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[12]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.3]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/8244.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/seo-prestashop-modules/8244-seo-disabled-and-deleted-301-redirect-products.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[8734]]></id><name><![CDATA[lgcookieslaw]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[EU Cookie Law (Notification Banner + Cookie Blocker)]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[THE ONLY MODULE THAT ALLOWS YOU TO FULLY COMPLY WITH THE EU COOKIE LAW]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[THE ONLY MODULE THAT ALLOWS YOU TO FULLY COMPLY WITH THE EU COOKIE LAW. Display a responsive and customized warning banner and disable cookies when users enter your website until you obtain their consent.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Our module fully complies with the European Cookie Law.    Complete compliance with the law    Besides displaying a warning banner, our module is the only one that allows you to block the cookies when users enter your store. As established by the law, you "shall ensure that the storing of information, or the gaining of access to information already stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user is only allowed on condition that the subscriber or user concerned has given his or her consent, having been provided with clear and comprehensive information."    Please note that all the other cookie modules sold on Addons only allows you to display a warning banner regardless of the user consent. Cookies are installed on the users' computer without obtaining their consent and regardless of their will.    Main features of the modules       Display a warning banner on every page to inform users about the use of cookies and ask for their consent   Disable a list of modules when users enter the website because warning users about cookies is useless and illegal if you have already installed cookies on their computer.   Enable these cookies after having obtained their consent or maintain them disabled if they refuse.   Fully customize the warning banner (colour, text, link, font, position, multilingual mode, transparency...)      Getting the user consent     The module includes 3 different ways to ask user consent, you can choose between:     Acceptance through a button: Users must click on the "I accept" button in the warning banner to give his consent. As soon as users give their consent, the warning banner disappears and all the modules using cookies will get enabled and will work as usual. But if users refuse to give their consent, the disabled modules will remain disabled.   Acceptance through the navigation (with banner disappearance): If users continue browsing the website, they will accept the use of cookies. The warning banner is displayed on the first page on which users arrive with a message like « By continuing browsing the website, you accept the use of cookies ». As soon as users decide to go to another page, the banner automatically disappears and the disabled modules will get enabled.   Acceptance through the navigation (without banner disappearance) : If users continue browsing the website, they will accept the use of cookies. Works the same as the previous option except the fact that the banner is always displayed and never disappears. The selected cookies will be disabled when users enter the store and will get enabled only when users will decide to go another page.    Note: the consent remains valid during the period of time set in the module interface (we recommend you not to go over 13 months)    Customizing the banner content and design    As recommended by the European authority, the module allows you to customize the warning message inside the banner (to inform users about the cookies users and their purpose) and add a "More information" button into the banner that take users to a CMS page of your store (to explain in details the use of cookies on your store).    The warning banner is responsive and will always be displayed full-width. The module comes with a Wysiwyg editor that allows you to fully customize the content of the banner (font, colour, effects, html code, links...). You can also choose from the configuration page the background colour of the banner, its percentage of opacity (transparency) and its position (top or bottom of the page). Moreover, the module is mutlilingual and automatially detects all the languages of your store, which allows you to set a different warning message per language.    Note: the module is designed to not display a warning message when search engines robots cawl you store in order not to affect your SEO.    Disabling the modules that use cookies    This is the only module that allows you to choose the modules/cookies that you want to disable until users give their consent. This feature is compulsory because it is useless and illegal to inform users if you have already installed cookied on their computer with their consent.    "Member States shall ensure that the storing of information, or the gaining of access to information already stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user is only allowed on condition that the subscriber or user concerned has given his or her consent, having been provided with clear and comprehensive information, in accordance with Directive 95/46/EC” EU Cookie Law    To comply with the directive of the EU Cookie Law, we recommend you to disable the tracking (Google Analytics), social sharing (Facebook " Like ", Google " +1 ", etc.) and targeted advertising modules. Please note that all modules that are required for the good running of your PrestaShop store (ex: basket cookie, session cookie...) don't require any consents.    Multistore mode    The module is compatible with multistore and allows you to display the same notification banner on each one of your shop but the consent is the same for all shops. If you accept the use of cookies on one of your shop, the module will consider that you accept the use of cookies for all your other shops (mention it on your cookie policy) and the notification banner will not be shown when you go to your other shops.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Línea Gráfica]]></author><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.13]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[117]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/8734.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/8734-eu-cookie-law-notification-banner-cookie-blocker.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[9783]]></id><name><![CDATA[gtrustedstores]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Google Trusted Stores]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Become a Google Trusted Stores certified merchant and let your customers benefit from Google&rsquo;s new and free e-commerce services. Conversion rate and repeat purchase increase guaranteed]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Become a Google Trusted Stores certified merchant and let your customers benefit from Google&rsquo;s new and free e-commerce services. Conversion rate and repeat purchase increase guaranteed.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Reassure your customers and increase your conversion rate and sales on your PrestaShop website by becoming a certified Google Trusted Stores merchant and be part of Google&rsquo;s latest e-commerce service.    By using this module in conjunction with our Google Merchant Center module (available separately on http://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-prestashop-modules/1768-Google-Merchant-Center.html), you will get the best possible results on the PrestaShop e-commerce platform.    This module is developed and published by Business Tech, Platinum Certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011 PrestaShop Awards for Best module.    You are guaranteed to buy a quality module and to get fast and efficient tech support in case you need it.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.13]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[4]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[5.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/9783.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[129.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/9783-google-trusted-stores.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[11345]]></id><name><![CDATA[pushoncart]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Push on Cart]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Easily increase your average cart value by offering customized discounts to your client in the shopping cart summary !]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Easily increase your average cart value by offering customized discounts to your client in the shopping cart summary !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With the Push on Cart module:     Easily increase your customer&rsquo;s average cart value   Clear unsold products from your inventory   Get your customers to discover new products to create a need and even secure their loyalty   Create demand for new products   Capitalize on impulse purchases   Improve customer satisfaction and loyalty with customized discounts on select products    ]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[23]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/11345.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/pricing-promotion-prestashop-modules/11345-push-on-cart.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[16535]]></id><name><![CDATA[cartabandonmentpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Abandoned Cart Reminder Pro]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Improve your conversion rate by 15% (and more) with abandoned carts reminder emails!]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Improve your conversion rate by 15% (and more) with abandoned carts reminder emails!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[An automatic email is sent to customers each time they add products to their shopping cart but does not purchase. It reminds and encourages them to complete the order. It&rsquo;s beneficial and easy to use!&nbsp;     Automatically send one or more personalized emails to remind your customers about the contents of their cart. This helps turn abandoned carts into sales.   Easily create email templates tailored to match your online store&rsquo;s theme.    Also, you can now propose discounts directly via the email in order to remind your clients to finalize their purchases.&nbsp;    Abandoned Cart reminder Pro allows to easily add discounts on a product price or free shipping cost directly on the email depending on each clients cart amount.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[checkout]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.5.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[108]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.9]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/16535.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/checkout-modules/16535-abandoned-cart-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[16939]]></id><name><![CDATA[seoexpert]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Expert]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Increase site traffic by landing on first page search engine results!    This SEO Expert module automatically fills in both meta tags and social media meta tags to optimize your online store for bette]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Increase site traffic by landing on first page search engine results!    This SEO Expert module automatically fills in both meta tags and social media meta tags to optimize your online store for better visibility on search engines and social media platforms.  Take the opportunity to buy it at launch cost!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Automatically create meta tags to save over 40 hours!  With the SEO Expert module:     Appear on first page results on search engines like Google, Bing, Yahoo, Yandex, etc.   Multiply your sales with increased web traffic   Improve visibility for each language of your store   Increase your conversions with qualified traffic   Differentiate your store with fully customized rules for product and category pages   Leverage Facebook and Twitter to acquire even more customers   Optimize your online store for social media with adapted shared titles    ]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.22]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[59]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/16939.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[219.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/seo-prestashop-modules/16939-seo-expert.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[17452]]></id><name><![CDATA[giftcards]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Gift Card]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Increase your sales and get more customers by offering them the chance to give the perfect gift with no risks with the Gift Card module developed by PrestaShop!&nbsp;  Practical and simple, gift cards]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Increase your sales and get more customers by offering them the chance to give the perfect gift with no risks with the Gift Card module developed by PrestaShop!&nbsp;  Practical and simple, gift cards are at the top of the list of the most given gifts!  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This solution provides the possibility of offering gift cards for any amount you like in your store.&nbsp;  Every customer can buy your gift cards to offer people the chance to come and spend them in your store.&nbsp;  &nbsp;    This module allows you to:&nbsp;         Pick up new customers: gift card beneficiaries represent a market of new prospects you can&rsquo;t pass up!&nbsp;   Increase your sales: gift card beneficiaries often spend more than the amount bought on the card.&nbsp;   Encourage indecisive customers to buy: if you offer a simple gift, suitable for all targets, customers won&rsquo;t hesitate.&nbsp;        &nbsp;    The gift card market brings great success with consumers and its annual growth varies between 20% and 40%.  ]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[20]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.9]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/17452.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[124.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/pricing-promotion-prestashop-modules/17452-gift-card.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[18974]]></id><name><![CDATA[remarkety]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Remarkety - Email Marketing for PrestaShop]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Remarkety will help you grow sales by over 30% sending personalized and targeted emails based on customer behavior and purchase history]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Remarkety will help you grow sales by over 30% sending personalized and targeted emails based on customer behavior and purchase history.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Deliver Product Recommendations  Automatically suggest products your customers might like in emails to cross-sell and up-sell    Send Personalized Coupons  Send personalized coupon codes to your customers to increase purchase rate    Win Back Inactive Customers  Deliver emails that urge sleeping customers to visit your website and purchase    Recover Abandoned Carts  Automatically email customers with images, links and prices of products they left in their cart    Targeted Email Blasts &amp; Newsletters  Segment by customer behavior and purchases to send relevant and personalized emails    Beautiful Reporting Dashboard  Intuitive dashboard displays essential analytics including purchase rate on every campaign    HTML Template Editor  Use pre-made templates or design your own with the template editor    Proactive Feedback &amp; Marketing Ideas  Recieve weekly tuning adjustments to improve email campaign performance]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.13]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[0]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[0.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/18974.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/18974-remarkety-email-marketing-for-prestashop.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges/></module></modules>
